

CONTACT

+989119461359

amirjalally73@gamil.com

Tehran

https://amirjalali.vercel.app

SKILL

HTML/CSS
JAVASCRIPT
JAVASCRIPT ES6
REACT
RESPONSIVE
TYPESCRIPT
NEXTJS
REDUX
RESTful APIS
UNIT TEST
REACT TEST LIBRARY
SASS
MATERIAL UI
TAILWINDCSS

LANGUAGE

English

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF LAW PMU 2013-2016

REACT BOOTCAMP MAPSA HR 2021-2022

AMIR FAMIL SAMMAK JALALI

Front End Developer

SUMMARY

Junior front-end developer with 1+ years of experience designing and building responsive web design in the financial industry. Proficient with CSS and JS Frameworks, with extensive knowledge of UX and user psychology. Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 18% with improved code and design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT END DEVELOPER

ARYANIC DADE - 2021-2022

 designing and performing websites for Iran national Gas company

FRONT END DEVELOPER

FREELANCER - 2020 -2021

- · Website design and development
- Delivered 9 websites from design to develop

PROJECTS

NEXT JS MOVIE APP GIT:https://github.com/amirjalalli/moviDB-app

REACT CART APP

GIT:https://github.com/amirjalalli/cartapp DEMO: https://cartap-project.vercel.app/

REACT PANEL ADMIN

GIT: https://github.com/amirjalalli/panel-dashboard DEMO: https://panel-dashboard.vercel.app/

REACT WATHER APP

GIT: https://github.com/amirjalalli/wather-app

DEMO:https://wather.vercel.app